[{"answer": " Why are you depressed, my friend", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Something he read, huh", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Something he read, huh", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "The universe is expanding", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No, I cannot.  You keep bringing it up, but I don't wanna live in a city where the only cultural advantage is that you can make a right turn on a red light", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm gonna meet her in front of the Beekman. I think I have a few minutes left.  Right", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Yeah, I do.  It's for my girl friend. Make it out to my friend", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "It's for my brudder.  my friend!  Hey!  This is my frien", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Bad mood?  I'm standing with the cast of", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Deal!  I'm dealing with two guys named Cheech", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Okay.  Please, I have a headache, all right", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm not getting my period.  my friend, every time anything out of the ordinary happens, you think that I'm getting my period", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "In the middle?  We'll only miss the titles.  They're in Swedish", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Two hours?  No, ", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hey, you ... everybody in line at the that place has to know our rate of intercourse", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " I'd like to hit this guy on a gut level", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh ... no, no, no, no, uh, uh.  No", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, well, let's see, there was my friend, from that place", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Look at you, yo", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well, yeah, you always look pretty, but that guy with you ..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Bad", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Right, right, so ", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "But th", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Well, bye. She laughs and backs up slowly toward the door", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Oh, yeah?  So do you.  Oh, God, whatt", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "No, um ... I was gonna take a cab", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You have a car?  So ...  I don't understand why ... if you have a car, so the", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " Oh, no, I have a car", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I don't ...  I don't ... Geez, I don't know, I've ... I w", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I'll getcha a piece", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Do I drive?  Uh, no, I gott", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "my friend, m", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Well ... thank you again", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh, you see an analyst", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Fifteen years", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Right.  Well, I don't know, I mean, uh, some of her poems seem", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Neat, yeah", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "-'cause, uh, you never know what's gonna happen", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Fifteen years, yeah", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Gee, boy, what do you have?  You have plague", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yeah, I meet a lotta jerks, too", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Really, do you think so, really", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "And we'll digest our food better", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Nothing that a few meg", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "My first... Yes, she was nice, but you know, uh, it was my fault.  I was just... I was too crazy", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "\"There goes another novel", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "No.  You're a wreck", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Really.  I mean it.  ", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Good?  I wa", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "No, I'm not", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Well, what doe", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Come on.  Yeah.  You know what?  You know, I like you, I really mean it.  I really do like you", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Do I love you", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Yeah, I know it's small", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " All right, granted, it has bad plumbing and bugs, but yo", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " All right, granted, it has bad plumbing and bugs, but yo", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Ho", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": " It'", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Hey, don't be ridiculous", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": " Yeah, grass, right?  The illusion that it will make a white woman more like Billie Holiday", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Me, no.  You ... ", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Yeah, but that's no", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Well, it ruins it for me if you have grass  because, you know, I'm, like, a comedia", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": " Is that a reason to steal from his father", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Yes, I know what I'm talking about", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Yeah, no food.  You know, we have to atone for our sins", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Tell you the truth, neither do we", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": " You followed me.  I can't believe it", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "You followed me", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "You followed me", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Well, what is your definition of following", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Why?  'Cause I ... was walkin' along a block behind you staring at you? That's not following", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": " Following is different.  I was spying", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "That's amazing. ", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "You cried?  I've never once cried. Fantastic ..", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": " Well, she said that I should probably come five times a week.  And you know something?  I don't think I mind analysis at all.  The only question is, Will it change my wife", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "Will it change my life", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Will it change your wife", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "Yeah, but you said,", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "Will it change my life", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "No, I didn't.  I said,", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "Yeah, but you said,", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "You said,", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": " my friend!  my friend!  I can't believe this", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "I'm following you and my friend, if yo", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "Why not?  You're always leaning on me to improve myself", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "I don't get a period!  I'm a cartoon character.  Can't I be upset once in a while", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": " I got the good chocolate, my friend", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "It really is lovely.  It's in the bathroom", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "Yeah, where is the spider", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "Is he in the bathroom", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": "Whatt", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": " Whatta you mean, don't go?  Whatt", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": " Oh, yeah, really, oh", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "Oh, neat ... oh, that's very nice, gosh, thanks a lot", "qsentId": 102}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 105, "question": " Hi, hi, my friend ..", "qsentId": 104}, {"answer": " Remember, we had that thing", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 107, "question": " Don't you remember w", "qsentId": 106}, {"answer": "What thing", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 109, "question": " Thing", "qsentId": 108}, {"answer": " That day in that place was the last day I remember really having a great time", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 111, "question": "Well, I've been moody and dissatisfied", "qsentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, you take a meeting with him, I'll take a meeting with you if you'll take a meeting with my friend", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 113, "question": "All the good meetings are taken", "qsentId": 112}, {"answer": "V.P.L.", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 115, "question": "Yeah, she's a ten, my friend, and that's great for you because you're", "qsentId": 114}, {"answer": "Visible panty line.  my friend, she is gorgeous", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 117, "question": "There are no twos, my friend", "qsentId": 116}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah?  Well, if she is, then the hell with her!  If she likes that lifestyle, let her live there!  He's a jerk, for one thing", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 119, "question": "Yeah. He ma", "qsentId": 118}, {"answer": "Sixteen years ago", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 121, "question": " Mean", "qsentId": 120}, {"answer": " So whatta you ... You're not gonna come back to that place", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 123, "question": "Hey, you didn't read", "qsentId": 122}, {"answer": " Twins, my friend.  Sixtee", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 125, "question": "Oh, I did my friend in the Park, my friend. I got mugged.  I was playing my friend the Second and two guys with leather jackets stole my leotard", "qsentId": 124}, {"answer": "You're a thinking person.  How can you choose this lifestyle", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 127, "question": "You didn't read", "qsentId": 126}, {"answer": "What is so incredibly great about that place?  It's a dying city!  Yo", "docId": "Annie-Hall.txt", "asentId": 129, "question": "Well, you only give me books with the word", "qsentId": 128}]